rotochamp.com 2015-12-04

# RotoChamp Privacy Policy

## Pivacy Policy

###### What This Privacy Policy Covers

This policy covers how RotoChamp treats personal information that RotoChamp collects and receives, including information related to your past use of RotoChamp products and services. Personal information is information about you that is personally identifiable like your name, address, email address, or phone number, and that is not otherwise publicly available. 

###### Information Collection and Use

RotoChamp collects personal information when you purchase RotoChamp, when you use RotoChamp website, when you visit RotoChamp pages or the pages of certain RotoChamp partners. RotoChamp may combine information about you that we have with information we obtain from business partners or other companies. 

RotoChamp automatically receives and records information on our server logs from your browser, including your IP address, RotoChamp cookie information, and the page you request. 

RotoChamp uses information for the following general purposes: to customize the advertising and content you see, fulfill your requests for products and services, improve our services, and contact you if you have selected to be contacted. 

###### Information Sharing and Disclosure

RotoChamp does not rent, sell, or share personal information about you with other people or nonaffiliated companies. 

We will transfer information about you if RotoChamp is acquired by or merged with another company. In this event, RotoChamp will notify you before information about you is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy. 

RotoChamp displays advertisements that are targeted based on personal information. Advertisers may assume that people who interact with, view, or click on targeted ads meet the targeting criteria - for example, women ages 18-24 from a particular geographic area. 

RotoChamp does not provide any personal information to the advertiser when you interact with or view a targeted ad. However, by interacting with or viewing an ad you are consenting to the possibility that the advertiser will make the assumption that you meet the targeting criteria used to display the ad. 

###### Cookies

RotoChamp may set and access RotoChamp cookies on your computer. 

RotoChamp lets other companies that show advertisements on some of our pages set and access their cookies on your computer. Other companies' use of their cookies is subject to their own privacy policies, not this one. Advertisers or other companies do not have access to RotoChamp's cookies. 

###### Third Party Advertisers

We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our web site. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp. 

Your Ability to Edit and Delete Your Account Information and Preferences 

We reserve the right to send you certain communications relating to the RotoChamp service, such as service announcements, administrative messages and the RotoChamp Newsletter, that are considered part of your RotoChamp account, without offering you the opportunity to opt-out of receiving them. 

###### Confidentiality and Security

We limit access to personal information about you to employees who we believe reasonably need to come into contact with that information to provide products or services to you or in order to do their jobs. 

###### Changes to this Privacy Policy

RotoChamp may update this policy. We will notify you about significant changes in the way we treat personal information by sending a notice to the primary email address specified in your RotoChamp account or by placing a prominent notice on our site. 

* * *
